afrohouseking.com 2019-05-17

# Terms, Conditions & Privacy • Afro House King

**By accessing this Website, you agree to these terms and policies and we have the right to change our policies that will take effect immediately.**

## Privacy

**AFROHOUSEKING**

This site and its owners take a proactive approach to user privacy and to ensure that necessary steps are taken to protect the privacy of its users throughout their experience when visiting the site.

**Use of Cookies**

This site uses cookies to enhance the user experience when visiting the site. Cookies are small files saved on a user’s computer that analyze, store, and store information about interactions and use of the website. This allows the website through your server to provide users with a personalized experience within this website.

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

**Contact & Information (Contact Forms and Subscriptions)**

Users contacting this site or its owners or subscribing to our newsletter do so at their own risk and by providing personal information at their own risk. Your personal information is kept confidential and stored securely for a certain period determined by us. No information will be disclosed without the user’s consent, and your information is used so that we may contact you about any request made or to have an idea of the demographics of our website.

**Comments**

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymised string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: <https://automattic.com/privacy/>. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

If you comment with your Facebook account, We decide the public who can see your comment or like it. If our audience is public, your comment will also be public. (Privacy Policy of Facebook comment service: <https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation>).

**Embedded content from other websites**

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, music, files, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

**Adverts (Ads)**

Our partners will collect your data and use cookies for ad personalization and measurement. If you are not sure how your data is collected or what is collected check the cookies section above for that information.

**Analytics**

Afro House King uses third party services to collect analytical data on our website. The Google Analytics service is used and if you would like to know how your information and data are collected for analytical data, the Google Analytics service privacy policy is available here:

<https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=pt>  
<https://policies.google.com/privacy>

**Who we share your data with and Where we send your data  
**

We don’t share or send your data with any partners, services or any individual. As said your data is kept secret and safe, we use it to improve our services, user experience and to get into contact with you in any situation.

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

**How long we retain your data and**

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognise and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

**What rights you have over your data**

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes. In the event that your information is leaked, stolen or hacked, we have the right to inform you and the GDPR authorities about the situation.

**How we protect your data**

Your data is kept very secure as we use the latest technological security measures such as the use of firewall, Two-Factor Authentication and CDN systems. In addiction to all that, our staff is trained in data protection.

## Terms of Responsibility

**Copyright notice.**

We control all copyrights and other intellectual property rights on our site and the material on our site.

The music and images on our website are for promotional purposes only, we do not claim any content like ours and we will not be responsible for any illegal use of the content. In case of infringement of copyright or intellectual property, contact us first to remove your property.

**External Links**

The owners of this site can not guarantee or verify the content of any linked site externally despite their best efforts. Users should therefore click on external links at their own risk and this site and its owners shall not be liable for any damages or implications caused by any external links mentioned.
